const trivia = [
  { // 1
    question: "Which year was the first printing press set up in Cambridge on this date?",
    answers: ["1639", "1529", "1765", "1694"]
  },
  { // 2
    question: "What year did the first British bus service begin on this date?",
    answers: ["1897", "1880", "1901", "1924"]
  },
  { // 3
    question: "What year on this date was the international slavery convention signed by 20 states?",
    answers: ["1920", "1925", "1926", "1896"]
  },
  { // 4
    question: "What year did Billy Graham begin his LA Crusade on this date?",
    answers: ["1947", "1949", "1951", "1943"]
  },
  { // 5
    question: "When did the Battle of Stamford Bridge take place?",
    answers: ["1066", "982", "1200", "898"]
  },
  { // 6
    question: "When was the US Bill of Rights passed on this date?",
    answers: ["1789", "1790", "1791", "1792"]
  },
  { // 7
    question: "When was the Twelth Amendment to the Constitution made on this date?",
    answers: ["1804", "1797", "1807", "1811"]
  },
  { // 8
    question: "When was Sequoia National Park established on this date?",
    answers: ["1890", "1878", "1860", "1934"]
  },
  { // 9
    question: "When did the groundbreaking ceremony begin for Fenway Park in Boston on this date?",
    answers: ["1911", "1960", "1980", "1999"]
  },
  { // 10
    question: "When did President Woodrow Wilson suffer a breakdown on this date in Pueblo, Colorado?",
    answers: ["1919", "1923", "1918", "1914"]
  },
  { // 11
    question: "When was the 40 hour workweek announced by Henry Ford on this date?",
    answers: ["1926", "1910", "1899", "1860"]
  },
  { // 12
    question: "When was the Royal Jordanian Air Force founded on this date?",
    answers: ["1955", "2005", "1902", "1924"]
  },
  { // 13
    question: "When was the Soviet Seven-Year Plan announced on this date?",
    answers: ["1957", "1969", "1979", "1989"]
  },
  { // 14
    question: "When was Sandra Day O'Connor (1st female Supreme Court Justice) sworn in on this date?",
    answers: ["1981", "1979", "1999", "2001"]
  },
  { // 15
    question: "When did Egypt & Jordan regain diplomatic relations on this date?",
    answers: ["1984", "1950", "1999", "1945"]
  },
  { // 16
    question: "When did General Sitiveni Rabuka stage a Fiji coup on this date?",
    answers: ["1987", "2010", "2005", "2000"]
  },
  { // 17
    question: "When did the UN Security Council vote to impose an air embargo on Iraq on this date?",
    answers: ["1990", "1988", "2000", "1980"]
  },
  { // 18
    question: "When did Young Sheldon begin premering?",
    answers: ["2017", "2014", "2010", "2020"]
  },
  { // 19
    question: "When was French President Nicolas Sarkozy sentenced to prison on this date?",
    answers: ["2025", "2007", "1985", "1978"]
  },
  { // 20
    question: "When did the Singapore announce its facial verification on this date, the first in the world?",
    answers: ["2020", "2018", "2016", "2023"]
  },
  { // 21
    question: "When did Beijing's Daxing International Airport open on this date?",
    answers: ["2019", "2024", "2022", "2015"]
  },
  { // 22
    question: "When did two Instagram Co-founders resign from Instagram/Facebook on this date?",
    answers: ["2018", "2015", "2013", "2011"]
  },
  { // 23
    question: "When did the Celtic Tiger (Ireland's extreme period of economic growth) first fall into recession?",
    answers: ["2008", "2009", "1989", "1990"]
  },
  { // 24
    question: "When did the Japense Tokachi-Oki earthquake take place on this date?",
    answers: ["2003", "2020", "2024", "2010"]
  },
  { // 25
    question: "When did Paramount @ Madison Square Garden in NYC open on this date?",
    answers: ["1991", "1989", "2015", "2020"]
  }
];
